Take a bite out of summer.
Ozark Sharks is a action, horror, science fiction film directed by Misty Talley.
A picturesque family vacation to the Ozarks goes sideways when a group of bull sharks show up
just in time for the big fireworks festival that the town holds every year.
Molly, played by Allisyn Snyder.
Rick, played by Michael Papajohn.
Curtis, played by Ross Britz.
Dawn, played by Ashton Leigh.
Jones, played by Thomas Francis Murphy.
Diane, played by Laura Cayouette.
Ozark Sharks is a 2016 American made-for-television horror
thriller film that aired on Syfy on July 28, 2016.
The TV film is written by Marcy Holland and Greg Mitchell, directed by Misty Talley, and starring Allisyn Ashley Arm,
Dave Davis, Michael Papajohn, Ross Britz, Ashton Leigh, Thomas Francis Murphy, and Laura Cayouette.
The film explores themes of shark attack, shark, woman director, ozarks.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.